Over the last seven years, most states have banned texting by drivers, and public service campaigns have tried a wide range of methods to persuade people to put down their phones when they are behind the wheel.
过去七年里，大多数州都已禁止司机发短信，公益宣传活动也尝试了各种各样的方法，劝说人们开车时放下手机。
Yet the problem, by just about any measure, appears to be getting worse.
然而，几乎无论用什么标准衡量，这个问题似乎都在恶化。
Americans are still texting while driving, as well as using social networks and taking photos.
美国人仍然边开车边发短信，还会使用社交网络、拍照。
Road accidents, which had fallen for years, are now rising sharply.
道路交通事故此前多年一直在减少，如今正急剧上升。
That is partly because people are driving more, but Mark Rosekind, the chief of the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration, said distracted driving was “only increasing, unfortunately.”
这在一定程度上是因为人们开车开得更多了，但美国国家公路交通安全管理局局长马克·罗斯金德表示，分心驾驶“很遗憾，只增不减”。
“Big change requires big ideas,” he said in a speech last month, referring broadly to the need to improve road safety.
“大变革需要大思路，”他上个月在一次演讲中说。这番话泛指道路安全有待改善。
So to try to change a distinctly modern behavior, lawmakers and public health experts are reaching back to an old approach: They want to treat distracted driving like drunk driving.
因此，为了设法改变一种明显带有现代特征的行为，立法者和公共卫生专家正回过头去借鉴一种老办法：他们想要像对待酒驾一样对待分心驾驶。
An idea from lawmakers in New York is to give police officers a new device called the Textalyzer.
纽约州立法者提出的一个想法是，给警察配备一种叫作 Textalyzer（“短信检测仪”）的新设备。
It would work like this: An officer arriving at the scene of a crash could ask for the phones of the drivers and use the Textalyzer to check in the operating system for recent activity.
设想中的用法是这样的：警察赶到车祸现场后，可以要求涉事司机交出手机，并用 Textalyzer 检查手机操作系统里最近的使用记录。
The technology could determine whether a driver had just texted, emailed or done anything else that is not allowed under New York’s hands-free driving laws.
这项技术能判定司机是否刚刚发过短信、电子邮件，或做过纽约州免提驾驶法律所不允许的其他任何事情。
“We need something on the books that can change people’s behavior,” said Félix W. Ortiz, who pushed for the state’s 2001 ban on hand-held devices by drivers.
“我们需要一条能改变人们行为的法规，”费利克斯·W.奥尔蒂斯说。他曾推动纽约州在2001年出台法令，禁止司机使用手持设备。
If the Textalyzer bill becomes law, he said, “people are going to be more afraid to put their hands on the cell phone.”
他说，如果 Textalyzer 法案成为法律，“人们会更不敢碰手机”。